Guide to the Institute for the Future Reports M1186
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Accession 2017-188 (Boxes 13-48)
  - Domestic Satellite Network Series Lipinski, Andrew J., 1980-11-01 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Scenes from Possible Futures (Provocation for a P&G Retreat) Johansen, Robert, 1980-09-01 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Workshop Proceedings Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Lipinski, Andrew J., 1979-10-01 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Strategic Issues, 1979-12-01 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - The Impact of an Energy Shortfall, 1980-1990, Volume I, 1979-12-01 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - The Impact of an Energy Shortfall, 1980-1990, Volume II, 1979-12-01 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Forecasting Domestic Demand for Textiles (E.I. du Pont Je Nemours & Company), 1980-03-01 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Picturephone Meeting Service Market Identification Model (AT&T) Lipinski, Andrew J., 1980-04-01 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Recent Experience with Video Teleconferencing—Lessons for ARCO (Atlantic Richfield) Johansen, Robert, 1980-05-01 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - The Changing Nature of Participation Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1980-07-01 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Picturephone Meeting Service Market Identification Model—An Addendum Report Lipinski, Andrew J., 1980-07-01 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - An Evaluation of Lifeline (Arthur Vining Davis Foundation) Palmer, Michael Tydeman, John, 1980-08-01 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - A Snapshot View of Communication Patterns (New Hampshire Division of Vocational Rehabilitation) Nyhan, Michael J. Charles, Jeff Vian, Kathleen, 1982-07-01 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Television Equipment Study, Final Report Plummer, Robert P., 1980-12-01 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - The Changing Nature of Participation Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1980-12-01 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Satellite Business Systems Teleconferencing Johansen, Robert Charles, Jeff, 1981-04-01 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - World Use of Satellite Photovoltaic Cells Lipinski, Andrew J., 1981-05-01 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Feasibility of Teleconferencing at American Express Company Charles, Jeff, 1981-05-01 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Corporate Communications (1981-1985) Amara, Roy Lipinski, Andrew J., 1981-08-01 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - The Boundaries of the U.S. Future (1981-1985) (Tracy-Locke) (Phillips Petroleum) Lipinski, Andrew J., 1981-09-01 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - The Use of KSIM in Technology Forecasting of Advanced Compsites Lipinski, Andrew J., 1982-01-01 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - The Changing Nature of Participation Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1981-11-01 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Commercial Airlines’ Demand for Jet Fuel in the United States Lipinski, Andrew J., 1982-01-01 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Price Waterhouse Tasks Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Amara, Roy, 1982-02-01 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Price Waterhouse Tasks (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Price Waterhouse Tasks (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Price Waterhouse Tasks (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations Regarding the Idea of Village Teleconference Centers for North Slope Villages Vian, Kathleen Johansen, Robert, 1982-06-01 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Health Care Services Environment Tydeman, John Poulin, Mary, 1982-06-01 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Home Information Management Services, 1982-1990 (AT&T) Adler, Richard, 1942- Lipinski, Hubert M., 1982-06-01 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Picturephone Meeting Service Marketing Identification Model Lipinski, Andrew J., 1982 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Future Market Needs and Technology Development, Stage 1 (Kimberly-Clark) Palmer, Michael, 1982-06-01 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Case Studies—Final Report (P&G, Aetna, New Hampshire) Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1982-06-01 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Needs for Electronic Office Tools in CIGNA Corporate Operations Johansen, Robert, 1982-04-01 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Strategic Plan for Teleconferencing (Bell Canada) Johansen, Robert, 1981-12-01 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - User Needs for Multimedia Systems, Interim Report (Multiclient) Johansen, Robert, 1982-07-01 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - The Market for Teletext in the United States (Draft Final) Tydeman, John Adler, Richard, 1942- Lipinski, Hubert M., 1982-10-01 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Five Industry Forecasts for Tosco Lipinski, Andrew J., 1982-10-01 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Health Care Services Environment Poulin, Mary, 1982-10-01 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Feasibility Study for the Promenades Office Complex, Hilton Head Island, South Carolina—Interim Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1982-12-01 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Marketing Prospects for the Promenade Office Complex, Hilton Head Island, South Carolina Adler, Richard, 1942- Palmer, Michael, 1983-03-01 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - An Approach to Needs Assessment for Possible Use by GTEDS Johansen, Robert, 1983-01-01 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Long-Term Outlook for Production of Fibers, Fabric, and Apparel Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1983-01-01 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - A Market Forecast for Advanced Multimedia Systems Lipinski, Hubert M., 1983-02-01 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Background Material for Graphic Arts Symposium—Draft Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1983-03-01 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Advanced Multimedia Systems Test 1-BNR Johansen, Robert, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Using Electronic Media to Improve the Professional Development Seminar Functions Johansen, Robert, 1981-10-01 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Multimedia Test 2 (GSEB) Plummer, Robert P. Lipinski, Hubert M., 1983-06-01 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Update on the Market for Teletext in the United States Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1983-06-01 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - VBI Teletext, Full Channel Teletext, and Videotex Adler, Richard, 1942- Tydeman, John, 1982-07-01 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Multimedia System Report, Draft Lipinski, Hubert M. Plummer, Robert P., 1983-08-01 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Interim Report for Pacific Telephone Bhambhra, R., 1983-09-01 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Prospects for Graphics in Teleconferencing Outlook Year 1 Research Report #1 Bhambhra, R. Johansen, Robert Gold, E., 1983-10-01 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Trend Cluster Generation for Feminine Care Long-Range Needs, Draft (Kimberly-Clark) Poulin, Mary, 1983-10-01 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Keycom McNeal, Barbara Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1983-10-01 (Box 40, Folder 12-13)
  - Implementation and Evaluation Strategies for Citibank Teleconferencing Systems Charles, Jeff, 1983-11-01 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Multimedia Field Test 3 Johansen, Robert Charles, Jeff, 1983-11-01 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Phillips’ Strategic Planning Lipinski, Andrew J., 1983-11-01 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Needs Assessment Seminar Methodology Johansen, Robert, 1983-11-01 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - The Promise and Pitfalls of Electronic Shopping (Garrett) Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1983-11-01 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Advanced Information Systems in Multinational Corporations Amara, Roy Lipinski, Andrew J., 1983-11-01 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Market Study of Keyfax Interactive Information Service Adler, Richard, 1942- McNeal, Barbara Allen, Dot, 1983-11-01 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Assessment of User Needs for an In-House Videotex System Adler, Richard, 1942- Allen, Dot, 1983-11-01 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Strategic Scenarios for Three End-Use Markets Lipinski, Andrew J., 1983 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Business Opportunities for Bridges in Teleconferencing Johansen, Robert Goldberg, JoAnne, 1984-01-01 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Aetna Case Study—Outlook Report Charles, Jeff, 1984-01-01 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Teleconferencing Johansen, Robert, 1984-01-01 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Introducing Teleconferencing in an Office Automation Environment—Outlook Case Study #2 (Lockheed) Allen, Dot, 1984-01-01 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Hospital Utilization to 1995 Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Poulin, Mary, 1984-03-01 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Videotex Entry Strategies Adler, Richard, 1942- Allen, Dot Goldberg, JoAnne, 1984-03-01 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Identifying Applications, and Feasibility for Video Teleconferencing at Pratt & Whitney Charles, Jeff, 1984-04-01 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Status of Teleconferencing Report Gold, Elliot M., 1944-, 1984-03-01 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - 1985-89 Price Differentials Lipinski, Andrew J., 1984 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Macroenvironmental Forecasts, Industry Trends, Teleservices Outlook Report #1 Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1985-01-01 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Competitive Analysis of the Teleconferencing marketplace (Teleconference Outlook, Year 2, Report #2) Gold, Elliot M., 1944-, 1985-01-01 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Changing Office Environments Over the Next 10 Years Goldberg, JoAnne Johansen, Robert, 1985-02-01 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Status Report, Year 2, Teleconference Outlook Gold, Elliot M., 1944-, 1985-04-01 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Technology Trends Report (Teleconference Outlook) Adler, Richard, 1942- Bhambhra, R. Mittman, Robert, 1985-05-01 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Final Report, Applelink Evaluation (Apple Computer) McNeal, Barbara Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1985-05-01 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Estimates of Alternatives to Pacific Bell Services (Pacific Bell) Amara, Roy Lipinski, Andrew J., 1984-09-01 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Business Care Report—Marketing of Telecoferencing (Teleconference Outlook, Year 2, Report #4) Charles, Jeff Goldberg, JoAnne Johansen, Robert, 1985-05-01 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Home Market Trends, 1985-90, Final Report (Apple Computer) Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1985-08-01 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Computer Conferencing at Eastman Kodak Company Results and Recommendations from Early Users (Eastman Kodak) Johansen, Robert McNeal, Barbara, 1985-06-01 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Market Forecast for Teleconferencing (Teleconference Outlook, Year 2, Report #5) Goldberg, JoAnne Johansen, Robert Charles, Jeff, 1985-07-01 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Teleservices Outlook Consumer Report (Teleservices Outlook) Adler, Richard, 1942- McNeal, Barbara Allen, Dot, 1985-07-01 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Business Market for Teleservices (Teleservices Outlook, #4 Lucas, Barbara G., 1985-08-01 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Forecast Diskette (Teleconference Outlook, Year 2, Report #6) Goldberg, JoAnne Gold, Elliot M., 1944-, 1985-08-01 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Industry Trends (Teleservices Outlook) Saffo, Paul Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Scenarios—Teleservices Outlook, Report #7) Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1985-11-01 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - The Market for Cough Syrup 1985-1995 (Jordan, Case, Taylor & McGrath Poulin, Mary, 1985-09-01 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - PP&L’s Future Market Environment, 1985-2005, Overview Report (Pacific Power & Light) Mittman, Robert Lipinski, Andrew J. Amara, Roy Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1985-10-01 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - PP&L’s Future Market Environment, 1985-2005, Technical Report (Pacific Power & Light) Amara, Roy, 1985-10-01 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Legal and Regulatory Issues Affecting Tele­services (Teleservices Outlook) Saffo, Paul Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1985-10-01 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Analysis of the Travel Agency Market for a Videotex Service (Tymnet) Adler, Richard, 1942- McNeal, Barbara, 1985-10-01 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - People Communicating Through Computers (Teleconference Outlook, Year 3, Report #1) Goldberg, JoAnne Johansen, Robert, 1985-11-01 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Planning for the Institute Morrison, J. Ian, 1952-, 1986-01-01 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Pacific Bell’s Market Environment, 1985-1995—Two Preliminary Scenarios (Pacific Bell) Amara, Roy Allen, Dot Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1986-01-01 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Opportunities in the U.S. Health Care Market, 1986–2000 (Pilkington Bros.) Poulin, Mary Lipinski, Andrew J., 1986-02-01 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Competitive Analysis (Teleconference Outlook, Year 3) Gold, Elliot M., 1944- Goldberg, JoAnne Johansen, Robert, 1986-01-01 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - New Product Generation (Donnelley Directory) Allen, Dot Johansen, Robert, 1986-02-01 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Selected Initiatives for New Enterprise Development (PPL) Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Morrison, J. Ian, 1952- Mittman, Robert, 1986-02-01 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Warehouse Data Systems/Teli Truck Terminal (Digitel) Lucas, Barbara G., 1986-02-01 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Home Banking Interchange Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1986-02-01 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - User/Non-User Research Report (Teleconference Outlook, Year 3) Charles, Jeff Gold, Elliot M., 1944- McNeal, Barbara Johansen, Robert, 1986-03-01 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Electronics Mittman, Robert Saffo, Paul, 1986-03-01 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Apparel Lucas, Barbara G. Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1986-03-01 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Needs Assessment for Video Teleconferencing (Kaiser Permanente) Charles, Jeff McNeal, Barbara, 1986-04-01 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Vision 2000 Issues for Ameritech (Ameritech) Adler, Richard, 1942- Allen, Dot, 1986-05-01 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Outlook Status Report (Teleconference Outlook, Year 3, Report #4) Gold, Elliot M., 1944-, 1986-05-01 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Food Retailing in the Next Decade (Campbell-Mithun, Inc.) Poulin, Mary Allen, Dot, 1986-05-01 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Cost Component Study (State of California) Mittman, Robert, 1986-05-01 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Future Scan Allen, Dot Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1986-05-01 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Summary of Workshop for Corporate Administration Allen, Dot Johansen, Robert, 1986-05-01 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Summary of Workshop with PFSD Allen, Dot Johansen, Robert, 1986-05-01 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Summary of Workshop for EBD (Aetna Life Insurance Co.) Allen, Dot, 1986-05-01 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - A Guide for Implementing Teleservices (Aetna Life Insurance Co.) Johansen, Robert Adler, Richard, 1942- Allen, Dot, 1986-06-01 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Summary of Broadscan Effort on Home of the Future (Procter & Gamble) Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1986-07-01 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Community Teleconferencing Centers, Phase II (North Slope Borough) Charles, Jeff McNeal, Barbara, 1986-06-01 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Report to Respondents to Survey on Channel Systems in the Food Retailing Industry (Procter & Gamble) Johansen, Robert Allen, Dot Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1986-06-01 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - People Communicating Through Computers, Teleconference Outlook, Year 3, Report #2) Mittman, Robert, 1986-07-01 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - International Teleconferencing Report (Teleconference Outlook, Year 3) Charles, Jeff, 1986-08-01 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - "Conclusions and Recommendations from the Metaphor Test, Draft Evaluation of User Experience from Corporate Decision Support Systems Business Test, Final (Procter & Gamble)" Johansen, Robert Saffo, Paul McNeal, Barbara, 1986-09 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Introduction to Channel Systems (Teleservices Outlook) Adler, Richard, 1942- Allen, Dot Lucas, Barbara G. McNeal, Barbara, 1986-09-01 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - The Market for Fixed and Transportable Up­links, 1986-2000. A Look at Ad Hoc, Special Programming and Dedicated Business Television Network (Teleservices Outlook, Year 4 Mittman, Robert Charles, Jeff Johansen, Robert Gold, Elliot M., 1944-, 1986-10-01 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - International Security Markets in the 1990s, Final (AMEX) Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Saffo, Paul, 1986-11-01 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Consumer Market Strategies—Scenarios and Implications (Ameritech) Adler, Richard, 1942- Saffo, Paul, 1985-06-01 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - The Market for Cordials and Liqueurs (Jordan, Manning, Case, Taylor & McGrath) McNeal, Barbara Lucas, Barbara G., 1986-11-01 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Commerical Insurance Division (Aetna Life & Casualty) Adler, Richard, 1942- Allen, Dot, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Personal Financial Security Division (Aetna Life & Casualty) Adler, Richard, 1942- Allen, Dot, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Employee Benefits Division (Aetna Life & Casualty) Adler, Richard, 1942- Allen, Dot, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Electronic Meetings and Artificial Intelligence Saffo, Paul Johansen, Robert, 1986-12-01 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Channel Systems in the Insurance Industry (Teleservices Outlook, Report #2) Allen, Dot Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1986-12-01 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Opportunities for Alaska in Selected Business/Profession and Financial Services (Kidder-Peabody) Schmid, Gregory, 1940- McNeal, Barbara Lucas, Barbara G., 1986-12-01 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Channel Systems in the Insurance Industry, Report to Respondents (Teleservices Outlook) Allen, Dot Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1986-12-01 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Information Needs Interviews (Mead Data Central) Adler, Richard, 1942- Lucas, Barbara G. McNeal, Barbara, 1987-01-01 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Interim Report Lucas, Barbara G., 1987-01-01 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - The Low End Group III Facsimile Market in the United States Lucas, Barbara G., 1987-02-01 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Applelink Competitive Assessment (Apple) Lucas, Barbara G. Allen, Dot Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1987-01-01 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Applelink Competitive Assessment (Apple) (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Client Capsules (Health Care Outlook) Allen, Dot Morrison, J. Ian, 1952-, 1987-01-01 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Teleservices for the Commercial Insurance Di­vision Allen, Dot Adler, Richard, 1942- Johansen, Robert, 1987-01-01 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Teleservices for the Personal Financial Security Division Allen, Dot Adler, Richard, 1942- Johansen, Robert, 1987-01-01 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Teleservices for the Employee Benefits Division Allen, Dot Adler, Richard, 1942- Johansen, Robert, 1987-01-01 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Two Scenarios Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1987-02-01 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Minitel as Channel Systems (Teleservices Outlook, Report 3) Mittman, Robert Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1987-02-01 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Health Care Outlook, 1st Quarter 1987 (Health Care Outlook, Year 1) Morrison, J. Ian, 1952- Amara, Roy, 1987-02-01 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Competitive Analysis, Year 4 (Teleservice Outlook, Year 4, Report #2) Gold, Elliot M., 1944- Johansen, Robert Charles, Jeff, 1987-02-01 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - PC Fax in the Facsimile Market (Digitel) Lucas, Barbara G., 1987-03-01 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Opportunities in Telecommunications for Southern California Edison (SCE) Mittman, Robert, 1987-03-01 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - The Market for Home Information Services (Eastman Kodak/Denver Project) Adler, Richard, 1942- Allen, Dot, 1987-03-01 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Baseline Evaluation of Interclassroom Electronic Messaging (AT&T ComputerPals) Charles, Jeff, 1987-04-01 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Eastman Kodak Company Denver Project Workshop (Eastman Kodak) Allen, Dot Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1987-04-01 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Home Source Competitive Analysis (Eastman Kodak) Mittman, Robert Saffo, Paul, 1987-04-01 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Forecasts (Teleconference Outlook, Year 4, Report #4) Mittman, Robert Johansen, Robert, 1987-06-01 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Forecasts (Teleconference Outlook, Year 4, Report #4) (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Status of Teleconferencing, Calendar Year 1989 Gold, Elliot M., 1944- Saffo, Paul, 1990-06-01 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Health Care Outlook, Second Quarterly Report (Health Care Outlook, Year 1) Morrison, J. Ian, 1952- Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Amara, Roy, 1987-05-01 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Trends in Text-Based Decision-Support Systems (Procter & Gamble) Saffo, Paul, 1987-05-01 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - PRISM Marketing Strategy Allen, Dot, 1987-06-01 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Considerations for Hewlett-Packard Network Restructuring (Hewlett-Packard) Charles, Jeff, 1987-06-01 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Two European Health Care Scenarios (DuPont) Morrison, J. Ian, 1952- Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1987-07-01 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Executive Education on the Strategic Use of Information Technology (Procter & Gamble) Johansen, Robert Allen, Dot, 1987-07-01 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Market Potential for Packet Switching in the Bay Area (AT&T) Lucas, Barbara G. Mittman, Robert, 1987-07-01 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Channel Systems in the Health Care Industry (Teleservices Outlook, Channel Systems, Report #4) Adler, Richard, 1942-, 1987-07-01 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Electronic Meetings and Artificial Intelligence, Promising Product Ideas (Outlook, Year 4, Re­port #5) Saffo, Paul Johansen, Robert, 1987-07-01 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Concept Trial Computer-Based Interclassroom Messaging Charles, Jeff, 1987-09-01 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Posttrial Evaluation of Interclassroom Electronic Messaging, Volume Two, Data Appendix (AT&T) Charles, Jeff, 1987-08-01 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Posttrial Evaluation of Interclassroom Electronic Messaging, Volume Two, Data Appendix (AT&T) (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Posttrial Evaluation of Interclassroom Electronic Messaging, Volume Two, Data Appendix (AT&T) (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - “Insight” Focus Groups (Mead Data Central) Adler, Richard, 1942- McNeal, Barbara, 1978-07-01 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Health Care Outlook Annual Report and Executive Summary (Health Care Outlook, Year 1) Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Amara, Roy Morrison, J. Ian, 1952-, 1987-08-01 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Health Care Outlook Annual Report and Executive Summary (Health Care Outlook, Year 1) (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Channel systems in the Franchise Industry (Teleservices Outlook, Channel Systems, Re­port #5) McNeal, Barbara Lucas, Barbara G., 1987-08-01 (Box 48, Folder 3)